<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="animal_1_name">Virginia opossum</string>
    <string name="animal_1_des">(Didelphis virginiana), commonly known as the North American opossum,
        is the only marsupial found north of Mexico. Is typically referred
        to simply as a possum. It is a solitary and nocturnal animal about the size of a domestic cat.
        https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Virginia_opossum
    </string>

    <string name="animal_2_name">American beaver</string>
    <string name="animal_2_des">(Castor canadensis) is one of two extant beaver species (the other being
        the Eurasian beaver, Castor fiber). It is native to North America, the species is often referred
        to simply as "beaver"
        https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/North_American_beaver
    </string>

    <string name="animal_3_name">Brown rat</string>
    <string name="animal_3_des">(Rattus norvegicus), also known as the common rat, street rat, sewer rat,
        Hanover rat, Norway rat, Norwegian rat, Parisian rat or wharf rat, is one of the best known and
        most common rats.
        https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Brown_rat
    </string>

    <string name="animal_4_name">Common muskrat</string>
    <string name="animal_4_des">(Ondatra zibethicus), the only species in genus Ondatra and tribe
        Ondatrini, is a medium-sized semiaquatic rodent native to North America.
        The muskrat is found in wetlands over a wide range of climates and habitats.
        https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Muskrat
    </string>

    <string name="animal_5_name">Eastern chipmunk</string>
    <string name="animal_5_des">(Tamias striatus) is a chipmunk species found in eastern North America.
        It is the only living member of the chipmunk subgenus Tamias, sometimes recognized as a separate genus.
        The name "chipmunk" comes from the Ojibwe word ajidamoo, which translates literally as one
        who descends trees headlong.
        https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Eastern_chipmunk
    </string>

    <string name="animal_6_name">Eastern fox squirrel</string>
    <string name="animal_6_des">(Sciurus niger), also known as the eastern fox squirrel, is the
        largest species of tree squirrel native to North America.
        https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fox_squirrel
    </string>

    <string name="animal_7_name">Eastern gray squirrel</string>
    <string name="animal_7_des">(Sciurus carolinensis), also known as the grey squirrel depending on
        region, is a tree squirrel in the genus Sciurus. It is native to eastern North America, where
        it is the most prodigious and ecologically essential natural forest regenerator.
        https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Eastern_gray_squirrel
    </string>

    <string name="animal_8_name">House mouse</string>
    <string name="animal_8_des">(Mus musculus) is a small mammal of the order Rodentia, characteristically
        having a pointed snout, large rounded ears, and a long and hairy tail. It is one of the most
        abundant species of the genus Mus.
        https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/House_mouse
    </string>

    <string name="animal_9_name">Meadow vole</string>
    <string name="animal_9_des">(Microtus pennsylvanicus), sometimes called the field mouse or meadow mouse,
        is a North American vole found across Canada, Alaska and the northern United States.
        https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Meadow_vole
    </string>

    <string name="animal_10_name">Red squirrel</string>
    <string name="animal_10_des">(Sciurus vulgaris) is a species of tree squirrel in the genus Sciurus
        common throughout Eurasia. The red squirrel is an arboreal, omnivorous rodent.
        https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Red_squirrel
    </string>

    <string name="animal_11_name">Southern flying squirrel</string>
    <string name="animal_11_des">(Glaucomys volans) is one of three species of the genus Glaucomys and
        one of three flying squirrel species found in North America. It is found in deciduous and mixed
        woods in the eastern half of North America.
        https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Southern_flying_squirrel
    </string>

    <string name="animal_12_name">White-footed mouse</string>
    <string name="animal_12_des">(Peromyscus leucopus) is a rodent native to North America.
        It is also known as the woodmouse. https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/White-footed_mouse</string>

    <string name="animal_13_name">Groundhog</string>
    <string name="animal_13_des">(Marmota monax), also known as a woodchuck, is a rodent of the family
        Sciuridae, belonging to the group of large ground squirrels known as marmots. https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Groundhog
    </string>

    <string name="animal_14_name">Eastern cottontail rabbit</string>
    <string name="animal_14_des">(Sylvilagus floridanus) is a New World cottontail rabbit, a member
        of the family Leporidae. It is the most common rabbit species in North America.
        https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Eastern_cottontail</string>

    <string name="animal_15_name">Eastern mole</string>
    <string name="animal_15_des">(Scalopus aquaticus) is a medium-sized, overall grey North American
        mole and the only member of the genus Scalopus. Its large, hairless, spade-shaped forefeet
        are adapted for digging. https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Eastern_mole</string>

    <string name="animal_16_name">Northern short-tailed shrew</string>
    <string name="animal_16_des">(Blarina brevicauda) is the largest shrew in the genus Blarina,
        and occurs in the northeastern region of North America. It is a semifossorial, highly active,
        and voracious insectivore and is present in a variety of habitats like broadleaved and pine
        forests among shrubs and hedges as well as grassy river banks.
        https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Northern_short-tailed_shrew</string>

    <string name="animal_17_name">Big brown bat</string>
    <string name="animal_17_des">(Eptesicus fuscus) is a species of vesper bat distributed widely
        throughout North America, the Caribbean, and the northern portion of South America. They are nocturnal,
        foraging for prey at night and roosting in sheltered areas during the day such as caves, tunnels,
        tree cavities, and human structures. https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Big_brown_bat</string>

    <string name="animal_18_name">Little brown bat</string>
    <string name="animal_18_des">(Myotis lucifugus) is a species of mouse-eared microbat found in
        North America. It has a small body size and glossy brown fur. Despite its name, the little brown
        bat is not closely related to the big brown bat, which belongs to a different genus.
        https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Little_brown_bat</string>

    <string name="animal_19_name">Northern long-eared bat</string>
    <string name="animal_19_des">(Myotis septentrionalis) </string>

    <string name="animal_20_name">American mink</string>
    <string name="animal_20_des">(Neovison vison) is a semiaquatic species of mustelid native to North America.
        The American mink is a carnivore that feeds on rodents, fish, crustaceans, frogs, and birds.
        https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/American_mink
    </string>

    <string name="animal_21_name">Bobcat</string>
    <string name="animal_21_des">(Lynx rufus) is a medium-sized North American cat. The bobcat is an
        adaptable predator that inhabits wooded areas, as well as semidesert, urban edge, forest edge,
        and swampland environments.</string>

    <string name="animal_22_name">Coyote</string>
    <string name="animal_22_des"> (Canis latrans) is a species of canine native to North America. It
        is smaller than its close relative, the gray wolf, and slightly smaller than the closely related
        eastern wolf and red wolf. https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Coyote
    </string>

    <string name="animal_23_name">Least weasel</string>
    <string name="animal_23_des">(Mustela nivalis), little weasel, common weasel, or simply weasel,
        is the smallest member of the genus Mustela, family Mustelidae and order Carnivora.
        https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Least_weasel
    </string>

    <string name="animal_24_name">Long-tailed weasel</string>
    <string name="animal_24_des">(Mustela frenata), also known as the bridled weasel or big stoat,
        is a species of mustelid distributed from southern Canada throughout all the United States and
        Mexico, southward through all of Central America and into northern South America.
        https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Long-tailed_weasel
    </string>

    <string name="animal_25_name">Raccoon</string>
    <string name="animal_25_des">(Procyon lotor) is a medium-sized mammal native to North America.
        The raccoon is the largest of the procyonid family. Three of the raccoon"'"s most distinctive
        features are its extremely dexterous front paws, its facial mask, and its ringed tail.
        https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Raccoon
    </string>

    <string name="animal_26_name">Red fox</string>
    <string name="animal_26_des">(Vulpes vulpes) is the largest of the true foxes and one of the most
        widely distributed members of the order Carnivora, being present across the entire Northern
        Hemisphere from the Arctic Circle to North Africa, North America and Eurasia. https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Red_fox</string>

    <string name="animal_27_name">River otter</string>
    <string name="animal_27_des">(Lontra canadensis), also known as the northern river otter or the
        common otter, is a semiaquatic mammal endemic to the North American continent found in and
        along its waterways and coasts. https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/North_American_river_otter</string>

    <string name="animal_28_name">Striped skunk</string>
    <string name="animal_28_des">(Mephitis mephitis) is a skunk of the genus Mephitis that occurs across most of North America. Striped
        skunks are polygamous omnivores with few natural predators, save for birds of prey. Like all skunks,
        they possess highly developed, musk-filled scent glands to ward off predators. https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Striped_skunk</string>

    <string name="animal_29_name">White-tailed deer</string>
    <string name="animal_29_des">(Odocoileus virginianus) is a medium-sized deer native to North America,
        Central America, Ecuador, and South America https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/White-tailed_deer
    </string>


</resources>