<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="bird_1_name">Pied-billed Grebe</string>
    <string name="bird_1_des">(Podilymbus podiceps) is a species of the grebe family of water birds.
        Since the Atitlán grebe (Podilymbus gigas) has become extinct, it is the sole extant member
        of the genus Podilymbus. The pied-billed grebe is primarily found in ponds throughout the Americas.
        https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pied-billed_grebe</string>

    <string name="bird_2_name">Horned Grebe</string>
    <string name="bird_2_des"> (Podiceps auritus) is a relatively small waterbird in the family Podicipedidae.
        There are two known subspecies: P. a. auritus, which breeds in the Palearctic, and P. a. cornutus, which
        breeds in North America. The Eurasian subspecies is distributed over most of northern Europe and the Palearctic,
        breeding from Greenland to western China.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Horned_grebe  </string>

    <string name="bird_3_name">Double-crested Cormorant</string>
    <string name="bird_3_des">(Phalacrocorax auritus) is a member of the cormorant family of seabirds.
        Its habitat is near rivers and lakes as well as in coastal areas, and is widely distributed across
        North America, from the Aleutian Islands in Alaska down to Florida and Mexico. Measuring 70–90 cm (28–35 in)
        in length, it is an all-black bird which gains a small double crest of black and white feathers in breeding season.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Double-crested_cormorant  </string>

    <string name="bird_4_name">American Bittern</string>
    <string name="bird_4_des">(Botaurus lentiginosus) is a species of wading bird in the heron family.
        It has a Nearctic distribution, breeding in Canada and the northern and central parts of the United
        States, and wintering in the U.S. Gulf Coast states. It is a well-camouflaged, solitary brown bird that
        unobtrusively inhabits marshes and the coarse vegetation at the edge of lakes and ponds.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/American_bittern </string>

    <string name="bird_5_name">Least Bittern</string>
    <string name="bird_5_des"> (Ixobrychus exilis) is a small heron, the smallest member of the family
        Ardeidae found in the Americas. The least bittern is one of the smallest herons in the world, with
        perhaps only the dwarf bittern and the black-backed bittern averaging smaller in length.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/American_bittern </string>

    <string name="bird_6_name">Great blue heron</string>
    <string name="bird_6_des">(Ardea herodias) is a large wading bird in the heron family Ardeidae,
        common near the shores of open water and in wetlands over most of North America and Central America
        , as well as the Caribbean and the Galápagos Islands. It is a rare vagrant to coastal Spain, the Azores,
        and areas of far southern Europe.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Great_blue_heron </string>

    <string name="bird_7_name">Great egret</string>
    <string name="bird_7_des">  (Ardea alba), also known as the common egret, large egret, great white egret
        or great white heron is a large, widely distributed egret, with four subspecies found in Asia, Africa,
        the Americas, and southern Europe. Distributed across most of the tropical and warmer temperate regions
        of the world, it builds tree nests in colonies close to water.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Great_egret</string>

    <string name="bird_8_name">Snowy Egret</string>
    <string name="bird_8_des">(Egretta thula) is a small white heron. The genus name comes from the Provençal
        French for the little egret aigrette, a diminutive of aigron, "heron". The species name thula is the Araucano
        for the black-necked swan, applied to this species in error by Chilean naturalist Juan Ignacio Molina in 1782.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Snowy_egret </string>

    <string name="bird_9_name">Green heron</string>
    <string name="bird_9_des">(Butorides virescens) is a small heron of North and Central America. Butorides is
        from Middle English butor "bittern" and Ancient Greek -oides, "resembling", and virescens is Latin for "greenish".
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Green_heron </string>

    <string name="bird_10_name">Trumpeter swan</string>
    <string name="bird_10_des">(Cygnus buccinator) is a species of swan found in North America. The heaviest
        living bird native to North America, it is also the largest extant species of waterfowl with a wingspan
        that may exceed 10 ft (3.0 m).
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Trumpeter_swan </string>

    <string name="bird_11_name">Tundra swan</string>
    <string name="bird_11_des"> (Cygnus columbianus) is a small Holarctic swan. The two taxa within it are usually
        regarded as conspecific, but are also sometimes split into two species: Bewick\'s swan (Cygnus bewickii)
        of the Palaearctic and the whistling swan (C. columbianus) proper of the Nearctic.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tundra_swan </string>

    <string name="bird_12_name">Greater white-fronted goose</string>
    <string name="bird_12_des">(Anser albifrons) is a species of goose related to the smaller lesser
        white-fronted goose (A. erythropus). It is named for the patch of white feathers bordering the base of
        its bill, in fact albifrons comes from the Latin albus "white" and frons" forehead ".
 https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Greater_white-fronted_goose </string>

    <string name="bird_13_name">Canada goose</string>
    <string name="bird_13_des">(Branta canadensis) is a large wild goose species with a black head and neck,
        white cheeks, white under its chin, and a brown body. Native to arctic and temperate regions of North
        America, its migration occasionally reaches northern Europe. It has been introduced to the United Kingdom
        , Ireland, New Zealand, Argentina, Chile, and the Falkland Islands.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Canada_goose  </string>

    <string name="bird_14_name">Wood duck</string>
    <string name="bird_14_des">(Aix sponsa) is a species of perching duck found in North America. It is
        one of the most colorful North American waterfowl.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Wood_duck </string>

    <string name="bird_15_name">Mallard</string>
    <string name="bird_15_des">(Anas platyrhynchos) is a dabbling duck that breeds throughout the temperate
        and subtropical Americas, Eurosiberia, and North Africa and has been introduced to New Zealand, Australia
        , Peru, Brazil, Uruguay, Argentina, Chile, Colombia, the Falkland Islands, and South Africa. This duck belongs
        to the subfamily Anatinae of the waterfowl family Anatidae.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mallard </string>

    <string name="bird_16_name">American black duck</string>
    <string name="bird_16_des">(Anas rubripes) is a large dabbling duck in the family Anatidae. It was described
        by William Brewster in 1902. It is the heaviest species in the genus Anas, weighing 720–1,640 g (1.59–3.62 lb)
        on average and measuring 54–59 cm (21–23 in) in length with a 88–95 cm (35–37 in) wingspan.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/American_black_duck </string>

    <string name="bird_17_name">Gadwall</string>
    <string name="bird_17_des"> (Mareca strepera) is a common and widespread dabbling duck in the family Anatidae.
        The gadwall is 46–56 cm (18–22 in) long with a 78–90 cm (31–35 in) wingspan. The male is slightly larger than
        the female, weighing on average 990 g (35 oz) against her 850 g (30 oz).
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Gadwall </string>

    <string name="bird_18_name">Northern shoveler</string>
    <string name="bird_18_des"> (Spatula clypeata) is known simply in Britain as the shoveler, is a common and widespread
        duck. It breeds in northern areas of Europe and across the Palearctic and across most of North America, wintering in
        southern Europe, Africa, the Indian subcontinent, Southeast Asia, and Central, and northern South America. It is a rare
        vagrant to Australia.
 https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Northern_shoveler </string>

    <string name="bird_19_name">Blue-winged teal</string>
    <string name="bird_19_des"> (Spatula discors) is a species of bird in the duck, goose, and swan family Anatidae.
        One of the smaller members of the dabbling duckgroup, it occurs in North America, where it breeds from southern
        Alaska to Nova Scotia, and south to northern Texas.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Blue-winged_teal </string>

    <string name="bird_20_name">Green-winged teal</string>
    <string name="bird_20_des">(Anas carolinensis or Anas crecca carolinensis) is a common and widespread duck that
        breeds in the northern areas of North America except on the Aleutian Islands.  It is highly gregarious outside
        of the breeding season and will form large flocks. In flight, the fast, twisting flocks resemble waders.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Green-winged_teal </string>

    <string name="bird_21_name">American wigeon</string>
    <string name="bird_21_des"> (Mareca americana) is also called a baldpate, is a species of dabbling
        duck found in North America. Formerly assigned to Anas, this species is classified with the other
        wigeons in the dabbling duck genus Mareca.The American wigeon is a medium-sized bird; it is larger
        than a teal, but smaller than a pintail.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/American_wigeon  </string>

    <string name="bird_22_name">Northern pintail</string>
    <string name="bird_22_des">(Anas acuta) is a duck with wide geographic distribution that breeds in
        the northern areas of Europe and across the Palearctic and North America. It is migratory and winters s
        outh of its breeding range to the equator. This is a large duck, and the male\'s long central
        tail feathers give rise to the species\' English and scientific names.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Northern_pintail </string>

    <string name="bird_23_name">Canvasback</string>
    <string name="bird_23_des">(Aythya valisineria) is a species of diving duck, the largest found in
        North America. It is the largest species in the genus Aythya, being similar in size to a mallard
        but with a heavier and more compact build than it.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Canvasback </string>

    <string name="bird_24_name">Redhead</string>
    <string name="bird_24_des">(Aythya americana) is a medium-sized diving duck  is 37 cm (15 in) long
        with an 84 cm (33 in) wingspan. It belongs to the genus Aythya, together with 11 other described
        species. The redhead and the common pochard form a sister group which together is sister to the canvasback.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Redhead_(bird) </string>

    <string name="bird_25_name">Ring-necked duck</string>
    <string name="bird_25_des">(Aythya collaris) is a diving duck from North America commonly found in
        freshwater ponds and lakes. Ring-necked ducks are small to medium-sized diving ducks. The adult
        male is similar in color pattern to the Eurasian tufted duck, its relative. Males are a little
        bit bigger than the female.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ring-necked_duck </string>

    <string name="bird_26_name">Lesser scaup</string>
    <string name="bird_26_des">(Aythya affinis) is a small North American diving duck that migrates south
        as far as Central America in winter. It is colloquially known as the little bluebill or broadbill
        because of its distinctive blue bill. https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lesser_scaup </string>

    <string name="bird_27_name">Bufflehead</string>
    <string name="bird_27_des">(Bucephala albeola) is a small sea duck of the genus Bucephala, the goldeneyes.
        The bufflehead ranges from 32–40 cm (13–16 in) long and weighs 270–550 g (9.5–19.4 oz), with the drakes
        larger than the females. It rivals the green-winged teal as the smallest American duck.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bufflehead </string>

    <string name="bird_28_name">Hooded merganser</string>
    <string name="bird_28_des">(Lophodytes cucullatus) is a species of small diving duck. It is the only
        extant species in the genus Lophodytes. The bird is striking in appearance; both sexes have crests
        that they can raise or lower, and the breeding plumage of the male is handsomely patterned and coloured.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hooded_merganser  </string>

    <string name="bird_29_name">Ruddy duck</string>
    <string name="bird_29_des">(Oxyura jamaicensis) is a duck from North America and one of the stiff-tailed
        ducks. The hooded merganser is a sexually dimorphic species.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ruddy_duck </string>

    <string name="bird_30_name">Turkey vulture</string>
    <string name="bird_30_des"> (Cathartes aura) is also known in some North American regions as the turkey
        buzzard. The turkey vulture is a scavenger and feeds almost exclusively on carrion. It finds its
        food using its keen eyes and sense of smell, flying low enough to detect the gasses produced by the
        beginnings of the process of decay in dead animals.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Turkey_vulture  </string>

    <string name="bird_31_name">Osprey</string>
    <string name="bird_31_des">(Pandion haliaetus) is a diurnal, fish-eating bird of prey with a cosmopolitan
        range. It is a large raptor, reaching more than 60 cm (24 in) in length and 180 cm (71 in) across the
        wings. It is brown on the upperparts and predominantly greyish on the head and underparts.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Osprey </string>

    <string name="bird_32_name">Sharp-shinned hawk</string>
    <string name="bird_32_des"> (Accipiter striatus) is a small hawk, with males being the smallest
        hawks in the United States and Canada, but with the species averaging larger than some Neotropical
        species, such as the tiny hawk.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sharp-shinned_hawk </string>

    <string name="bird_33_name">Cooper’s hawk</string>
    <string name="bird_33_des">(Accipiter cooperii) is also known as the Cooper hawk, is a medium-sized
        hawk native to the North American continent and found from Southern Canada to Northern Mexico. This
        species is a member of the genus Accipiter, sometimes referred to as true hawks, which are famously
        agile, relatively small hawks common to wooded habitats around the world and also the most diverse
        of all diurnal raptor genera.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cooper%27s_hawk </string>

    <string name="bird_34_name">Red-shouldered hawk</string>
    <string name="bird_34_des">(Buteo lineatus) is a medium-sized hawk. Its breeding range spans eastern
        North America and along the coast of Californiaand northern to northeastern-central Mexico.
        Red-shouldered hawks are permanent residents throughout most of their range, though northern
        birds do migrate, mostly to central Mexico. The main conservation threat to the widespread species is deforestation.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Red-shouldered_hawk </string>

    <string name="bird_35_name">Red-tailed hawk</string>
    <string name="bird_35_des">(Buteo jamaicensis) is a bird of prey that breeds throughout most of
        North America, from the interior of Alaska and northern Canada to as far south as Panama and
        the West Indies. It is one of the most common members within the genus of Buteo in North America or worldwide.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Red-tailed_hawk </string>

    <string name="bird_36_name">Rough-legged hawk</string>
    <string name="bird_36_des">(Buteo lagopus), also called the rough-legged hawk, is a medium-large
        bird of prey. It is found in Arctic and Subarctic regions of North America and the Palearctic
        during the breeding season and migrates south for the winter. It was traditionally also known
        as the rough-legged falcon in such works as John James Audubon\'s The Birds of America.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Rough-legged_buzzard </string>

    <string name="bird_37_name">Bald eagle</string>
    <string name="bird_37_des">(Haliaeetus leucocephalus) is a bird of prey found in North America. A
        sea eagle, it has two known subspecies and forms a species pairwith the white-tailed eagle
        (Haliaeetus albicilla). Its range includes most of Canada and Alaska, all of the contiguous
        United States, and northern Mexico.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bald_eagle </string>

    <string name="bird_38_name">American kestrel</string>
    <string name="bird_38_des">(Falco sparverius) is the smallest and most common falcon in North America.
        It has a roughly two-to-one range in size over subspecies and sex, varying in size from about the
        weight of a blue jay to a mourning dove.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/American_kestrel </string>

    <string name="bird_39_name">Peregrine falcon</string>
    <string name="bird_39_des">(Falco peregrinus), also known as the peregrine, and historically as the
        duck hawk in North America, is a widespread bird of prey (raptor) in the family Falconidae. A
        large, crow-sized falcon, it has a blue-grey back, barred white underparts, and a black head.
        The peregrine is renowned for its speed, reaching over 320 km/h (200 mph) during its characteristic
        hunting stoop (high-speed dive).
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Peregrine_falcon </string>

    <string name="bird_40_name">Wild turkey</string>
    <string name="bird_40_des">(Meleagris gallopavo) is an upland ground bird native to North America,
        one of two extant species of turkey, and the heaviest member of the diverse Galliformes. It is
        the same species as the domestic turkey, which was originally derived from a southern Mexican
        subspecies of wild turkey (not the related ocellated turkey).
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Wild_turkey </string>

    <string name="bird_41_name">King rail</string>
    <string name="bird_41_des">(Rallus elegans) is a waterbird, the largest North American rail. Distinct
        features are a long bill with a slight downward curve, with adults being brown on the back and
        rusty-brown on the face and breast with a dark brown cap.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/King_rail </string>

    <string name="bird_42_name">Virginia rail</string>
    <string name="bird_42_des">(Rallus limicola) is a small waterbird, of the family Rallidae. These
        birds remain fairly common despite continuing loss of habitat, but are secretive by nature and
        more often heard than seen.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Virginia_rail </string>

    <string name="bird_43_name">Sora</string>
    <string name="bird_43_des">(Porzana carolina) is a small waterbird of the family Rallidae, sometimes
        also referred to as the sora rail or sora crake. The genus name Porzanais derived from Venetian
        terms for small rails, and Carolina refers to the Carolina Colony.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sora_(bird) </string>

    <string name="bird_44_name">American coot</string>
    <string name="bird_44_des">(Fulica americana), also known as a mud hen or pouldeau, is a bird of
        the family Rallidae. Though commonly mistaken for ducks, American coots are only distantly
        related to ducks, belonging to a separate order. Unlike the webbed feet of ducks, coots have
        broad, lobed scales on their lower legs and toes that fold back with each step in order to
        facilitate walking on dry land.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/American_coot </string>

    <string name="bird_45_name">Sandhill crane</string>
    <string name="bird_45_des">(Antigone canadensis) is a species of large crane of North America and
        extreme northeastern Siberia. The common name of this bird refers to habitat like that at the
        Platte River, on the edge of Nebraska\'s Sandhills on the American Plains.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sandhill_crane </string>

    <string name="bird_46_name">Killdeer</string>
    <string name="bird_46_des">(Charadrius vociferus) is a large plover found in the Americas. It was
        described and given its current scientific name in 1758 by Carl Linnaeusin the 10th edition of
        his Systema Naturae. There are three subspecies. The killdeer\'s common name comes from its often-heard
        call. Its upperparts are mostly brown with rufous fringes, the head has patches of white and black,
        and there are two black breast bands.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Killdeer </string>

    <string name="bird_47_name">Greater yellowlegs</string>
    <string name="bird_47_des">(Tringa melanoleuca) is a large North American shorebird. The genus name
        Tringa is the New Latin name given to the green sandpiper by Aldrovandus in 1599 based on Ancient
        Greek trungas, a thrush-sized, white-rumped, tail-bobbing wading bird mentioned by Aristotle. The
        specific melanoleuca is from Ancient Greek melas, "black", and leukos, "white".
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Greater_yellowlegs </string>

    <string name="bird_48_name">Lesser yellowlegs</string>
    <string name="bird_48_des"> (Tringa flavipes) is a medium-sized shorebird. The genus name Tringa is
        the New Latin name given to the green sandpiper by Aldrovandus in 1599 based on Ancient Greek trungas,
        a thrush-sized, white-rumped, tail-bobbing wading bird mentioned by Aristotle. The specific flavipesis
        from Latin flavus, "yellow", and pes, "foot".
 https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lesser_yellowlegs </string>

    <string name="bird_49_name">Solitary sandpiper</string>
    <string name="bird_49_des"> (Tringa solitaria) is a small shorebird. This species measures 18–23 cm
        (7.1–9.1 in) long, with a wingspan up to 50 cm (20 in) and a body mass of 31–65 g (1.1–2.3 oz).
        It is a dumpy waderwith a dark green back, greyish head and breast and otherwise white underparts.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Solitary_sandpiper </string>

    <string name="bird_50_name">Spotted sandpiper</string>
    <string name="bird_50_des">(Actitis macularius) is a small shorebird. Adults have short yellowish legs and an
        orange bill with a dark tip. The body is brown on top and white underneath with black spots. Non-breeding birds do
not have the spotted underparts, and are very similar to the common sandpiper of Eurasia.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Spotted_sandpiper</string>

    <string name="bird_51_name">Dunlin</string>
    <string name="bird_51_des">(Calidris alpina) is a small wader. An adult dunlin in breeding plumage shows the
        distinctive black belly which no other similar-sized wader possesses. The winter dunlin is basically grey above
        and white below. Juveniles are brown above with two whitish "V" shapes on the back.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dunlin</string>

    <string name="bird_52_name">Least sandpiper</string>
    <string name="bird_52_des">(Calidris minutilla) is the smallest known shorebird. They tend to breed in North
America on tundra or in bogs. They nest on the ground near water. The female lays four eggs in a shallow scrape lined
        with grass and moss. Both parents have been observed to incubate their eggs.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Least_sandpiper</string>

    <string name="bird_53_name">Pectoral sandpiper</string>
    <string name="bird_53_des">(Calidris melanotos) is a small, migratory wader. Pectoral sandpipers make their nest
by scraping a whole in the ground and with a thick lining, is deep enough to protect its four eggs from the cool breezes
        of its breeding grounds.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pectoral_sandpiper</string>

    <string name="bird_54_name">Wilson’s snipe</string>
    <string name="bird_54_des">(Gallinago delicata) is a small, stocky shorebird. The name of this bird is meant  to
        commemorate the American ornithologist Alexander Wilson. They breed in marshes, bogs, tundra and wet meadows in
        Canada and the northern United States and on the Chukchi Peninsula, Russia.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Wilson%27s_snipe</string>

    <string name="bird_55_name">American woodcock</string>
    <string name="bird_55_des">(Scolopax minor) is a small chunky shorebird species found primarily in the eastern
        half of North America. Woodcocks spend most of their time on the ground, partly due to the fact that their plumage
Provides extremely good camouflage.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/American_woodcock</string>

    <string name="bird_56_name">Ring-billed gull</string>
    <string name="bird_56_des">(Larus delawarensis) is a medium-sized gull. The ring-billed gulls\' breeding
        habitat is near lakes, rivers, or the coast in Canada and the northern United States. They nest colonially
        on the ground, often on islands. This bird tends to be faithful to its nesting site, if not its mate, from year to year.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ring-billed_gull</string>

    <string name="bird_57_name">Herring gull</string>
    <string name="bird_57_des">(Larus smithsonianus or Larus argentatus smithsonianus) is a large gull
        that breeds in North America. Adults are white with gray back and wings, black wingtips with white
        spots, and pink legs. Immature birds are gray-brown and are darker and more uniform than European herring
        gulls, with a darker tail.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/American_herring_gull</string>

    <string name="bird_58_name">Rock dove</string>
    <string name="bird_58_des">(Columba livia) is a member of the dove family, Columbidae. In common use, it is
Usually just referred to as a “pigeon”. Coloration varies between wild and domestic rock Doves. These birds are
        extremely common and widespread across most of the world.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Rock_dove</string>

    <string name="bird_59_name">Mourning dove</string>
    <string name="bird_59_des">(Zenaida macroura) is a member of the dove family, Columbidae. It’s also referred to
as the turtle dove. It is one of the most abundant and widespread of all North American birds. It is a gamebird, as
more than 20 million are killed annually for sport or for meat.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mourning_dove</string>

    <string name="bird_60_name">Black-billed cuckoo</string>
    <string name="bird_60_des">(Coccyzus erythropthalmus) is a New World species in the Cuculidae (cuckoo)
        family. The scientific name is from Ancient Greek. The genus name kokkuzo, means to call like a
        common cuckoo, and erythropthalmus is from eruthros, "red" and ophthalmos, "eye".
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Black-billed_cuckoo</string>

    <string name="bird_61_name">Yellow-billed cuckoo</string>
    <string name="bird_61_des">(Coccyzus americanus) is a species of cuckoo. They are also referred to as a Storm
crow, likely because they are known to sing on hot days, often before rain or thunder. Their range spans from North
America to South America, and can sometimes be seen in western Europe.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Yellow-billed_cuckoo</string>

    <string name="bird_62_name">Barred owl</string>
    <string name="bird_62_des">(Strix varia) is a large species of owl. These owls are native to eastern North America,
but have expanded their range all the way to the west coast, where they are considered an invasive species. Their
diet consists mostly of small mammals, but will prey upon almost any living creature that is small enough.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Barred_owl</string>

    <string name="bird_63_name">Common nighthawk</string>
    <string name="bird_63_des">(Chordeiles minor) is a medium sized bird in the nightjar family. These birds are
Nocturnal. However, their hunting process ends when dusk becomes night, and resumes again as night becomes
dawn. They will rarely feed in complete darkness.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Common_nighthawk</string>

    <string name="bird_64_name">Chimney swift</string>
    <string name="bird_64_des">(Chaetura pelagica) is a bird that belongs to the swift family Apodidae. The Chimney
            Swift is named after its soot-grey color, and has been placed in the vulnerable category, meaning it is currently a threatened species.
            https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Chimney_swift</string>

    <string name="bird_65_name">Ruby-throated hummingbird</string>
    <string name="bird_65_des">(Archilochus colubris) is a hummingbird that spends its time in eastern North America
during the summer to breed. The rest of the year, it is a resident of Central America, Mexico, and parts of Florida. It
is the most common hummingbird on the east of the Mississippi.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ruby-throated_hummingbird</string>

    <string name="bird_66_name">Belted kingfisher</string>
    <string name="bird_66_des">(Megaceryle alcyon) is a large, conspicuous water kingfisher. This bird is the only
member of its group that can be found in North America. Adult males are white and blue, while females are white and
grey.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Belted_kingfisher</string>

    <string name="bird_67_name">Red-headed woodpecker</string>
    <string name="bird_67_des">(Melanerpes erythrocephalus) is a small to medium sized woodpecker. It is native
to temperate North America. Up until 2018, this bird was considered to be near threatened, but has recently moved
back to the category of least concern, after habitat management stabilized their numbers.
 https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Red-headed_woodpecker</string>

    <string name="bird_68_name">Red-bellied woodpecker</string>
    <string name="bird_68_des">(Melanerpes carolinus) is a medium sized woodpecker. It belongs to the
        family Picidae. Although its name would indicate that it has a red belly, it does not. Instead,
        the Red-bellied woodpecker
is white and black with a red marking covering most of the head.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Red-bellied_woodpecker</string>

    <string name="bird_69_name">Downy woodpecker</string>
    <string name="bird_69_des">(Dryobates pubescens) is the smallest species of woodpecker in North America.
        They like to nest in dead trees or limbs, which are excavated by the nesting pair.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Downy_woodpecker</string>

    <string name="bird_70_name">Hairy woodpecker</string>
    <string name="bird_70_des">(Leuconotopicus villosus) is a medium sized woodpecker. They are colored
mostly black and white, and adults tend to have red patches on their head. They are permanent residents and only
migrate in extreme situations.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hairy_woodpecker</string>

    <string name="bird_71_name">Northern flicker</string>
    <string name="bird_71_des">(Colaptes auratus) is a medium sized bird in the woodpecker family. It
        is native to parts of North America, Central America, Cuba, and the Cayman Islands. It is one
        of the only woodpeckers that have
        been observed to migrate.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Northern_flicker</string>

    <string name="bird_72_name">Pileated woodpecker</string>
    <string name="bird_72_des">(Dryocopus pileatus) is a woodpecker that is native to North America. It is the second
        largest woodpecker on the continent. It gets the name “pileated” from its prominent, red-crested head, which comes
        from the word pileatus meaning "capped" in Latin.
        https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pileated_woodpecker</string>

    <string name="bird_73_name">Olive-sided flycatcher</string>
    <string name="bird_73_des">(Contopus cooperi) is a medium sized passerine bird of the tyrant flycatcher
        family. This bird has a very peculiar flight pattern, where it likes to fall sharply after climbing
        in altitude. These birds are labeled as near threatened, likely due to loss of habitat.
        https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Olive-sided_flycatcher</string>

    <string name="bird_74_name">Eastern wood-pewee</string>
    <string name="bird_74_des">(Contopus virens) is a small bird of the tyrant flycatcher family. It is native to North
America. However, it will migrate to Central America and the Andes region of South America during winter. Their
diet consists mainly of insects caught mid-flight.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Eastern_wood_pewee</string>

    <string name="bird_75_name">Yellow-bellied flycatcher</string>
    <string name="bird_75_des">(Empidonax flaviventris) is a small bird of the tyrant flycatcher family. They like to
breed in wet northern woods, particularly in spruce bogs. Their nests are typically formed in sphagnum moss near or
at ground level.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Yellow-bellied_flycatcher</string>

    <string name="bird_76_name">Acadian flycatcher</string>
    <string name="bird_76_des">(Empidonax virescens) is a small bird of the tyrant flycatcher family. They like to
breed in deciduous forests near water. During winter, these birds will migrate to eastern Mexico, the Caribbean,
and northwest South America.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Acadian_flycatcher </string>

    <string name="bird_77_name">Willow flycatcher</string>
    <string name="bird_77_des">(Empidonax traillii) is a small, neotropical bird of the tyrant flycatcher family. They
are migratory birds, and span from the west coast to the east coast of the United States, avoiding only the southeast
corner of the country.  There are four subspecies, three of which only breed in California.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Willow_flycatcher</string>

    <string name="bird_78_name">Eastern phoebe</string>
    <string name="bird_78_des">(Sayornis phoebe) is a small passerine bird. These bird are migratory, and can be
observed in the eastern portions of Central America, the U.S., and central areas of Canada. Some Eastern phoebes
have been seen in western Europe, but not very often.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Eastern_phoebe</string>

    <string name="bird_79_name">Great crested flycatcher</string>
    <string name="bird_79_des">(Myiarchus crinitus) is a large bird of the tyrant flycatcher family. These birds are
typically found in the treetops, and are rarely ever seen on the ground. Their song is called the dawn song, because
they typically sing at this time, searching for a mate.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Great_crested_flycatcher </string>

    <string name="bird_80_name">Eastern kingbird</string>
    <string name="bird_80_des">(Tyrannus tyrannus) is a large tyrant flycatcher. It is native to North America. Some
Eastern kingbirds have been observed leaving their nests out in the open, while others have a tendency to
thoroughly hide their nest location.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Eastern_kingbird </string>


    <string name="bird_81_name">White-eyed vireo</string>
    <string name="bird_81_des">(Vireo griseus) is a small songbird. These birds are known to eat insects, including
caterpillars, during breeding months. At other points in the year, they can be seen eating berries instead. They
tend to reside in eastern regions of the U.S., but will spend time farther south in places like eastern Mexico and  Central America.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/White-eyed_vireo </string>


    <string name="bird_82_name">Yellow-throated vireo</string>
    <string name="bird_82_des">(Vireo flavifrons) is a small American songbird. They are migratory, traveling as far
        south as the northernmost region of South America, and spending other parts of the year in the eastern region of
The U.S. Some of these birds have been observed in western Europe, but this is very rare.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Yellow-throated_vireo </string>

    <string name="bird_83_name">Warbling vireo</string>
    <string name="bird_83_des">(Vireo gilvus) is a small songbird. It’s song is noted to be cheerful, with slight
differences between western and eastern residing vireos. Some officials consider these two, the western and
eastern vireos, as two seperate species.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Warbling_vireo</string>

    <string name="bird_84_name">Red-eyed vireo</string>
    <string name="bird_84_des">(Vireo olivaceus) is a small American songbird. It bears a strong resemblance to
a warbler, but is not closely related however. They are colored olive-green and white, and are named after their
Distinctive red iris.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Red-eyed_vireo</string>

    <string name="bird_85_name">Blue jay</string>
    <string name="bird_85_des">(Cyanocitta cristata) is a large passerine bird of the family Corvidae. It is native to
North America, and resides mainly in the central and eastern portions of the United States. It will breed in both
deciduous and coniferous forests, and has been commonly observed in residential areas.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Blue_jay</string>

    <string name="bird_86_name">American crow</string>
    <string name="bird_86_des">(Corvus brachyrhynchos) is a large passerine bird of the family Corvidae. American
crows are very common and extremely widespread. Due to their susceptibility to the West Nile virus, they have been
        a useful bioindicator for humans to track the spread of the virus. Contrary to some beliefs, transmission of
        the virus
directly from crow to human is impossible.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/American_crow</string>

    <string name="bird_87_name">Barn swallow</string>
    <string name="bird_87_des">(Hirundo rustica) is the most widespread species of swallow known to man, and is
also a passerine bird. It is known for its blue coloration, and forked tail. There are six subspecies of the Barn swallow,
four of which are recorded as being strongly migratory. These birds are closely associated with humans, which
humans benefit from as well, due to their insect eating habits.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Barn_swallow</string>

    <string name="bird_88_name">Tree swallow</string>
    <string name="bird_88_des">(Tachycineta bicolor) is a bird in the family Hirundinidae. They are vibrant blue in
color, and females will typically be a little bit duller than males. The Tree swallow is a migratory bird, and will span
From Alaska, all the way to Mexico in the span of its life.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tree_swallow </string>

    <string name="bird_89_name">Purple martin</string>
    <string name="bird_89_des">(Progne subis) is the largest swallow in North America. Despite their name, they are not
        actually purple. However, they have an iridescent sheen that can cause them to appear in many different
colors. They are known for their speed and agility, and are regarded as very good flyers.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Purple_martin</string>

    <string name="bird_90_name">Northern rough-winged swallow</string>
    <string name="bird_90_des">(Stelgidopteryx serripennis) is a small swallow. It is a migratory bird that is
native to the U.S. and central america. These birds like to nest in the burrows of soil banks, but sometimes in
        caves or trees, and other times in human made formations like gutters and tubes.
</string>

    <string name="bird_91_name">Bank swallow</string>
    <string name="bird_91_des">(Riparia riparia) is a passerine bird in the swallow family. They are migratory, and
have an extremely wide range of habitats that span across most of the world. These birds usually nest directly
Into the ground, preferring a very specific kind of ground (known as loess) to burrow in.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sand_martin</string>

    <string name="bird_92_name">Cliff swallow</string>
    <string name="bird_92_des">(Petrochelidon pyrrhonota) is a passerine bird in the family Hirundinidae. These
birds are extremely social, and can be found nesting in colonies of 2,000 nests or more. They like to build their
nests close together, using vocalizations to warn others of danger and to communicate food availability.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/American_cliff_swallow</string>

    <string name="bird_93_name">Carolina chickadee</string>
    <string name="bird_93_des">(Poecile carolinensis) is a small passerine that belongs in the tit family Paridae.
During fall and winter migration, these birds tend to flock together, including many other kinds of species in the
flocks, such as titmice, nuthatches, and warblers. Other birds love chickadees because they call out when they
find good sources of food.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Carolina_chickadee</string>

    <string name="bird_94_name">Black-capped chickadee</string>
    <string name="bird_94_des">(Poecile atricapillus) is a small songbird. It is a passerine that belongs in the
tit family Paridae. These birds have a tendency to live in deciduous and mixed forests, spending their time on
tree branches foraging for food. They are also known to be non-migratory.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Black-capped_chickadee</string>

    <string name="bird_95_name">Brown creeper</string>
    <string name="bird_95_des">(Certhia americana) is a small songbird, and happens to be the only North
American bird that belongs in the treecreeper family Certhiidae. They tend to breed in Coniferous forests
in portions of Alaska and Canada, as well as the western and northeastern regions of the U.S..
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Brown_creeper</string>

    <string name="bird_96_name">Tufted titmouse</string>
    <string name="bird_96_des">(Baeolophus bicolor) is a small songbird that is a part of the tit and chickadee
Family. This bird is known to have a song that resembles a whistle, and can vary in 20 different observed ways.
The Tufted titmouse is non-migratory, and native to Ohio as well as Mississippi.
 https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tufted_titmouse</string>

    <string name="bird_97_name">White-breasted nuthatch</string>
    <string name="bird_97_des">(Sitta carolinensis) is a small songbird that belongs in the nuthatch family.
These birds are commonly seen in temperate portions of the United States. During winter months, they
tend to feed on seeds. But during other times of the year, will forage for insects on branches and trunks.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/White-breasted_nuthatch</string>

    <string name="bird_98_name">Sedge wren</string>
    <string name="bird_98_des">(Cistothorus stellaris) is a small passerine bird that belongs in the family
 Troglodytidae. These birds are often found in tall wetlands and meadows, because they like to nest in
tall grasses to feed on insects. Sedge wrens have been observed to improvise their songs rather than
learn to sing from other birds.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sedge_wren</string>

    <string name="bird_99_name">Marsh wren</string>
    <string name="bird_99_des">(Cistothorus palustris) is a small songbird that belongs in the wren family.
It is sometimes called the long-billed marsh wren to distinguish it from the shorter billed sedge wren. These
birds will typically forage near bodies of water, and will sometimes catch insects out of the air.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Marsh_wren</string>

    <string name="bird_100_name">Carolina wren</string>
    <string name="bird_100_des">(Thryothorus ludovicianus) Is a common species of wren that is located in
the eastern half of the United States, including some of south Canada and north Mexico as well. They prefer
to live in dense forests and suburban areas. This form of wren is the state bird of South Carolina.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Carolina_wren</string>

    <string name="bird_101_name">House wren</string>
    <string name="bird_101_des">(Troglodytes aedon) is an extremely small songbird, and a part of the wren
   family. They are the most widely distributed bird in the Americas. Their diet consists of butterfly
   larvae, spiders, snails, and other similar insects.
   https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/House_wren</string>

    <string name="bird_102_name">Golden-crowned kinglet</string>
    <string name="bird_102_des">(Regulus satrapa) is an extremely small songbird. It is in the family
   Regulidae, and lives in most of Northern America. Golden-crowned kinglets have been noted for their
   lack of fear for humans. They like to forage in trees and shrubs, where they eats insects, insect eggs,
   and spiders.
   https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Golden-crowned_kinglet</string>

    <string name="bird_103_name">Blue-gray gnatcatcher</string>
    <string name="bird_103_des">(Polioptila caerulea) is an extremely small songbird. While both sexes
   of these birds have differing color patterns, males and females both have a distinctive white ring
   that goes around each eye. They forage in trees and shrubs, eating things like insects, insect eggs,
   or even spiders.
   https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Blue-gray_gnatcatcher</string>

    <string name="bird_104_name">Eastern bluebird</string>
    <string name="bird_104_des">(Sialia sialis) is a small thrush. These birds tend to live in open woodlands
   farmlands, or orchards. They are very social, oftentimes flying in flocks of one-hundred or more.
   Their diet consists of insects, fruits, and berries. However, they favor grasshoppers, crickets, katydids,
   and beetles among other prey.
   https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Eastern_bluebird</string>

    <string name="bird_105_name">Veery</string>
    <string name="bird_105_des">(Catharus fuscescens) is a small member of the North American thrush
   species. During breeding season, they mainly eat insects. However, during summer and fall, their diet
   changes. At which point, they prefer fruits and berries.
   https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Veery</string>

    <string name="bird_106_name">Wood thrush</string>
    <string name="bird_106_des">(Hylocichla mustelina) is a North American passerine bird. The song
   sung by male Wood thrushes is highly regarded as the most beautiful in North America. Also, they
   tend to be territorial, and will defend large areas around its nest.
   https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Wood_thrush</string>

    <string name="bird_107_name">American robin</string>
    <string name="bird_107_des">(Turdus migratorius) is a migratory Songbird. Its named after its similarly
   colored counterpart, the European robin, although the two are not closely related. They have been
   known to breed very early in the year, and are typically the earliest bird to sing at dawn.
   https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/American_robin</string>

    <string name="bird_108_name">Gray catbird</string>
    <string name="bird_108_des">(Dumetella carolinensis) is a member of the family Mimidae. Its a North
   American and Central American perching bird, which was named for its cat-like song. They have been
   observed to interact with humans the most during winter months.
   https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Gray_catbird</string>

    <string name="bird_109_name">Northern mockingbird</string>
    <string name="bird_109_des">(Mimus polyglottos) is the only mockingbird that can be commonly found
   in North America. These birds like to stay put, but will migrate south if weather becomes too harsh
   during winter months.
   https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Northern_mockingbird</string>

    <string name="bird_110_name">Brown thrasher</string>
    <string name="bird_110_des">(Toxostoma rufum) is a member of the family Mimidae. It is the only thrasher
   that is known to live primarily east of central Texas. They are known to sing over 1000 song, which
   is the largest song repertoire of any kind of bird.
   https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Brown_thrasher</string>

    <string name="bird_111_name">Cedar waxwing</string>
    <string name="bird_111_des">(Bombycilla cedrorum) is a member of the family Bombycillidae. Cedar
   waxwings are known to be sociable and non-territorial, and can be seen grooming each other from time
   to time. Their flocks typically move place to place to find good sources of berries.
   https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cedar_waxwing</string>

    <string name="bird_112_name">European starling</string>
    <string name="bird_112_des">(Sturnus vulgaris) is a medium sized passerine bird of the starling family.
   Its known for its ability to mimic the songs of other bids. These birds are seen as beneficial for
   agriculture, because they control pest populations. In certain situations, however, they can be seen
   as a past themselves since they sometimes feed on fruit and crops.
   https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Common_starling</string>

    <string name="bird_113_name">Yellow warbler</string>
    <string name="bird_113_des">(Setophaga petechia) is a New World wabler. This bird is known for being
   extremely widespread, since it breeds in all of North America and some of northern South America.
   https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/American_yellow_warbler</string>

    <string name="bird_114_name">Yellow-rumped warbler</string>
    <string name="bird_114_des">(Setophaga coronata) is a combination of several different types of warblers.
   These birds are known to like coniferous and mixed coniferous-deciduous woodlands during breeding
   season. At other points in the year, they tend to stay in places like streamside woodlands, pine
   forests, or residential areas.
   https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Yellow-rumped_warbler</string>

    <string name="bird_115_name">Palm warbler</string>
    <string name="bird_115_des">(Setophaga palmarum) is a small songbird of the New World warbler family.
   This bird has two distinct subspecies that differ in color. One of these subspecies, known as the
   yellow palm warbler, is mostly yellow with some brown markings. On the other hand, its counterpart,
   the brown palm warbler, is mostly brown with some yellow markings.
   https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Palm_warbler</string>

    <string name="bird_116_name">American redstart</string>
    <string name="bird_116_des">(Setophaga ruticilla) is a New World warbler. These birds feed almost
   entirely on insects, which they either flycatch or glean from leaves. This species also has a skewed
   sex ratio that results in a large number of unmated males.
   https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/American_redstart</string>

    <string name="bird_117_name">Prothonotary warbler</string>
    <string name="bird_117_des">(Protonotaria citrea) is a small songbird of the New World warbler family.
   It is the only member of the genus Protonotaria. It is the only known eastern warbler that likes to
   nest in natural cavities, such as a woodpecker hole.
   https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Prothonotary_warbler</string>

    <string name="bird_118_name">Common yellowthroat</string>
    <string name="bird_118_des">(Geothlypis trichas) is a New World warbler. These birds like to breed
   in marshes, or other areas that are wet with dense low vegetation. Male yellowthroats have a black
   mask-like marking that covers their face. Females have been observed to choose males with the largest
   mask.
   https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Common_yellowthroat</string>

    <string name="bird_119_name">Yellow-breasted chat</string>
    <string name="bird_119_des">(Icteria virens) is a large songbird, native to North America. It is
   the only known member of the Icteriidae family. It used to be a member of the New World warbler
   family until 2017, when the American Ornithological Society decided it should be in its own.
   https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Yellow-breasted_chat</string>

    <string name="bird_120_name">Scarlet tanager</string>
    <string name="bird_120_des">(Piranga olivacea) is a medium sized American songbird. It is classified
   as a part of both the cardinal family, and the tanager family. It bears many similarities to cardinals,
   but lacks the conical bill that cardinals need for seed and insect eating.
   https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Scarlet_tanager</string>

    <string name="bird_121_name">Rose-breasted grosbeak</string>
    <string name="bird_121_des">(Pheucticus ludovicianus) is a large bird in the cardinal family that
   feeds mostly on seeds. These birds tend to live longer in captivity, since they often die in the
   wild by collision with things like buildings or cars.
   https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Rose-breasted_grosbeak</string>

    <string name="bird_122_name">Indigo bunting</string>
    <string name="bird_122_des">(Passerina cyanea) is a small bird in the cardinal family. It feeds mostly
   on seeds, and uses the stars to navigate when migrating. It has been observed interbreeding with
   the closely related Lazuli bunting bird when they cross paths.
   https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Indigo_bunting</string>

    <string name="bird_123_name">Northern cardinal</string>
    <string name="bird_123_des">(Cardinalis cardinalis) is a bird of the Cardinalis genus. They are
   the same as a common cardinal or cardinal. It has a distinctive crest on the head and a mask on the
   face. Males are very vibrantly red, and females have a faded red color.
   https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Northern_cardinal</string>

    <string name="bird_124_name">Eastern towhee</string>
    <string name="bird_124_des">(Pipilo erythrophthalmus) is a large bird that was formerly accepted as
   the same species as the Spotted Towhee. Before being identified as separate birds, they were both
   known as the rufous-sided towhee. the name "towhee" was derived from their very distinctive song.
   https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Eastern_towhee</string>

    <string name="bird_125_name">American tree sparrow</string>
    <string name="bird_125_des">(Spizelloides arborea) is also known as a Winter sparrow. It is a medium
   sized bird that prefers colder climates. It breeds in the northern limits of Alaska and Canada,
   but will migrate south to the bottom of Canada and all of the U.S. for winter.
   https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/American_tree_sparrow</string>

    <string name="bird_126_name">Chipping sparrow</string>
    <string name="bird_126_des">(Spizella passerina) is a type of American sparrow. It is widely spread
   across Northern America and mostly tame. It molts twice a year, meaning that it takes on different
   color patterns depending on if it is breeding season or not.
   https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Chipping_sparrow</string>

    <string name="bird_127_name">Field sparrow</string>
    <string name="bird_127_des">(Spizella pusilla) is a small bird in the family of Passerellidae. It
   can be seen in eastern portions of the United States and Canada. The habitat of this bird tends
   to be shrubs and grasslands. They tend to build nests on the ground, feeding mostly on seeds and insects.
   https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Field_sparrow</string>

    <string name="bird_128_name">Song sparrow</string>
    <string name="bird_128_des">(Melospiza melodia) is an extremely common, variable, and adaptive species
   from North America. They tend to have brown bodies with white underbellies, covered in black streaking.
   https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Song_sparrow</string>

    <string name="bird_129_name">Swamp sparrow</string>
    <string name="bird_129_des">(Melospiza georgiana) is medium sized and closely related to the (more
   well known) Song sparrow. They typically breed in marshes, where they build nests close to water level.
   Their diet consists mainly of fruit, seeds, and arthropods.
   https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Swamp_sparrow</string>

    <string name="bird_130_name">White-throated sparrow</string>
    <string name="bird_130_des">(Zonotrichia albicollis) is a species of passerine. They have been observed
   to have two distinct variations of coloring known as the tan striped, and the white striped forms.
   They tend to breed in Canada and New England but migrate to Mexico and eastern America in the winter.
   https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/White-throated_sparrow</string>

    <string name="bird_131_name">White-crowned sparrow</string>
    <string name="bird_131_des">(Zonotrichia leucophrys) is a species of passerine. It is native to
   North America and can be observed in almost all parts of it. These birds are typically grey with
   black and white striping on the head.
   https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/White-crowned_sparrow</string>

    <string name="bird_132_name">Dark-eyed junco</string>
    <string name="bird_132_des">(Junco hyemalis) is seen in temperate North America, but will venture
   as far as the Arctic in Summer months. These birds are known to have varying physical features.
   However, they are typically grey with white bellies.
   https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dark-eyed_junco</string>

    <string name="bird_133_name">Orchard oriole</string>
    <string name="bird_133_des">(Icterus spurius) is the smallest known icterid. It has been known to breed
   from northeast America to eastern Mexico, and will spend winters as far south as South America.
   https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Orchard_oriole</string>

    <string name="bird_134_name">Baltimore oriole</string>
    <string name="bird_134_des">(Icterus galbula) is a small icterid blackbird which is common to eastern
   regions of North America. The Baltimore oriole is know to interbreed with the western Bullocks oriole,
   leading to both being classified as a single species; the Northern Oriole.
   https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Baltimore_oriole</string>

    <string name="bird_135_name">Red-winged blackbird</string>
    <string name="bird_135_des">(Agelaius phoeniceus) is a passerine bird, or perching bird, which can
   be distinguished by the arrangement of their toes (3 forward 1 back). It has been argued to be one
   of the most abundant living land birds in North America. Due to the abundance of this bird, it tops
   the list as one of the most studied wild birds in the wild. Male and female red-winged blackbirds are
   colored completely different.
   https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Red-winged_blackbird</string>

    <string name="bird_136_name">Eastern meadowlark</string>
    <string name="bird_136_des">(Sturnella magna) is a medium sized bird. It is seen primarily in the
   eastern portions of North and South America. It is very similar in appearance to the western meadowlark,
   and is often mistaken as such. The difference in song from the western to eastern meadowlark is typically
   the easiest way to differentiate between the two.
   https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Eastern_meadowlark</string>

    <string name="bird_137_name">Common grackle</string>
    <string name="bird_137_des">(Quiscalus quiscula) is a large bird that can be found all around much
   of north America. It is commonly seen in large numbers. Groups of common Grackles are referred to as
   a "plague".
   https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Common_grackle</string>

    <string name="bird_138_name">Brown-headed cowbird</string>
    <string name="bird_138_des">(Molothrus ater) is a small bird that is native to subtropical North
   America. It is brood parasitic, meaning it relies on others to help raise their young. In winter,
   it may migrate south as far as Mexico.
   https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Brown-headed_cowbird</string>

    <string name="bird_139_name">House sparrow</string>
    <string name="bird_139_des">(Passer domesticus) is a part of the sparrow family. This bird is common
   to most parts of the world. Being that its been introduced to such a high number of regions around
   the globe, it is regarded as being THE most widely distributed wild bird. It can be found in a wide
   variety of habitats and climates, including urban environments.
   https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/House_sparrow</string>

    <string name="bird_140_name">American goldfinch</string>
    <string name="bird_140_des">(Spinus tristis) is a part of the finch family. It is known to be a
   migrative bird. During the winter, it can be found anywhere from the US-Canada border to Mexico.
   https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/American_goldfinch</string>

    <string name="bird_141_name">House finch</string>
    <string name="bird_141_des">(Haemorhous mexicanus) is a part of the finch family. It is originally
   native to western North America, but has since been introduced in the east as well as Hawaii.
   https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/House_finch</string>


</resources>