<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="tree_1_name">Tulip tree</string>
    <string name="tree_1_des">Liriodendron /ˌlaɪriəˈdɛndrən, ˌlɪr-, -ioʊ-/ is a genus of two species
        of characteristically large trees, deciduous over most of their populations, in the magnolia
        family (Magnoliaceae).
        https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Liriodendron
    </string>

    <string name="tree_2_name">Sycamore</string>
    <string name="tree_2_des">Platanus occidentalis, also known as American sycamore, American
        planetree, western plane, occidental plane, buttonwood, and water beech, is a species
        of Platanus native to the eastern and central United States.
        https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Platanus_occidentalis
    </string>

    <string name="tree_3_name">American elm</string>
    <string name="tree_3_des">Ulmus americana, generally known as the American elm or, less
        commonly, as the white elm or water elm,[a] is a species native to eastern North America.
        https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ulmus_americana
    </string>

    <string name="tree_4_name">American hackberry</string>
    <string name="tree_4_des">Celtis occidentalis, commonly known as the common hackberry, is a
        large deciduous tree native to North America. It is also known as the nettletree,
        sugarberry, beaverwood, northern hackberry, and American hackberry.
        https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Celtis_occidentalis
    </string>

    <string name="tree_5_name">Black walnut</string>
    <string name="tree_5_des">Juglans nigra, the eastern American black walnut, is a species of
        deciduous tree in the walnut family, Juglandaceae, native to North America.
        https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Juglans_nigra
    </string>

    <string name="tree_6_name">Bitternut hickory</string>
    <string name="tree_6_des">Carya cordiformis, the bitternut hickory,[2] also called bitternut or
        swamp hickory, is a large pecan hickory with commercial stands located mostly north of the
        other pecan hickories. Bitternut hickory is cut and sold in mixture with the true hickories.
        It is the shortest-lived of the hickories, living to about 200 years.
        https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Carya_cordiformis
    </string>

    <string name="tree_7_name">Shellbark hickory</string>
    <string name="tree_7_des">Carya laciniosa, the shellbark hickory, in the Juglandaceae or walnut
        family is also called shagbark hickory, bigleaf shagbark hickory, kingnut, big, bottom,
        thick, or western shellbark, attesting to some of its characteristics. It is a slow-growing,
        long-lived tree, hard to transplant because of its long taproot, and subject to insect
        damage. The nuts, largest of all hickory nuts, are sweet and edible.
        https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Carya_laciniosa
    </string>

    <string name="tree_8_name">Shagbark hickory</string>
    <string name="tree_8_des">Carya ovata, the shagbark hickory, is a common hickory in the Eastern
        United States and southeast Canada. It is a large, deciduous tree, growing well over 100 ft
        (30 m) tall, and can live more than 350 years.
        https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Carya_ovata
    </string>

    <string name="tree_9_name">American beech</string>
    <string name="tree_9_des">Fagus grandifolia, the American beech or North American beech, is the
        species of beech tree native to the eastern United States and extreme southeast Canada. The
        genus name Fagus is Latin for "beech", and the specific epithet grandifolia comes from
        grandis "large" and folium "leaf".
        https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fagus_grandifolia
    </string>

    <string name="tree_10_name">White oak</string>
    <string name="tree_10_des">Quercus alba, the white oak, is one of the preeminent hardwoods of
        eastern and central North America. It is a long-lived oak, native to eastern and central
        North America.
        https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Quercus_alba
    </string>

    <string name="tree_11_name">Bur oak</string>
    <string name="tree_11_des">Quercus macrocarpa, the bur oak, sometimes spelled burr oak, is a
        species of oak in the white oak section Quercus sect. Quercus, native to North America in
        the eastern and central United States.
        https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Quercus_macrocarpa
    </string>

    <string name="tree_12_name">Swamp white oak</string>
    <string name="tree_12_des">Quercus bicolor, the swamp white oak, is a North American species of
        medium-sized trees in the beech family. It is a common element of Americas north central and
        northeastern mixed forests. It can survive in a variety of habitats. It forms hybrids with
        bur oak where they occur together in the wild.
        https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Quercus_bicolor
    </string>

    <string name="tree_13_name">Shingle oak</string>
    <string name="tree_13_des">Quercus imbricaria, the shingle oak, is a deciduous tree in the red
        oak group of oaks. It is native primarily to the Midwestern and Upper South regions of
        North America.
        https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Quercus_imbricaria
    </string>

    <string name="tree_14_name">Black oak</string>
    <string name="tree_14_des">Quercus velutina, the eastern black oak or more commonly known as
        simply black oak, is a species of oak in the red oak (Quercus sect. Lobatae) group. It is
        widespread in eastern and central North America.
        https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Quercus_velutina
    </string>

    <string name="tree_15_name">Red oak</string>
    <string name="tree_15_des">Quercus rubra, the northern red oak, is an oak tree in the red oak
        group (Quercus section Lobatae). It is a native of North America, in the eastern and central
        United States.
        https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Quercus_rubra
    </string>

    <string name="tree_16_name">Pin oak</string>
    <string name="tree_16_des">Quercus palustris, the pin oak[4] or swamp Spanish oak, is an oak in
        the red oak section (Quercus sect. Lobatae). Pin oak is one of the most commonly used
        landscaping oaks in its native range due to its ease of transplant, relatively fast growth,
        and pollution tolerance.
        https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Quercus_palustris
    </string>

    <string name="tree_17_name">Eastern hophornbeam</string>
    <string name="tree_17_des">Ostrya virginiana, the American hophornbeam, is a species of Ostrya
        native to eastern North America.
        https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ostrya_virginiana
    </string>

    <string name="tree_18_name">Ironwood</string>
    <string name="tree_18_des">Carpinus caroliniana, the American hornbeam, is a small hardwood tree
        in the genus Carpinus. American hornbeam is also known as blue-beech, and musclewood. It is
        native to eastern North America.
        https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Carpinus_caroliniana
    </string>

    <string name="tree_19_name">Alder</string>
    <string name="tree_19_des">Alder is the common name of a genus of flowering plants, Alnus,
        belonging to the birch family Betulaceae.
        https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Alder
    </string>

    <string name="tree_20_name">American basswood</string>
    <string name="tree_20_des">Tilia americana is a species of tree in the family Malvaceae, native
        to eastern North America.
        https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tilia_americana
    </string>

    <string name="tree_21_name">Cottonwood</string>
    <string name="tree_21_des">opulus deltoides, the eastern cottonwood or necklace poplar, is a
        cottonwood poplar native to North America, growing throughout the eastern, central, and
        southwestern United States.
        https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Populus_deltoides
    </string>

    <string name="tree_22_name">Black willow</string>
    <string name="tree_22_des">Salix nigra, the black willow, is a species of willow native to
        eastern North America.
        https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Salix_nigra
    </string>

    <string name="tree_23_name">Wild black cherry</string>
    <string name="tree_23_des">Prunus serotina, commonly called black cherry, wild black cherry,
        rum cherry, or mountain black cherry, is a deciduous tree or shrub belonging to the
        genus Prunus. The species is widespread and common in North America and South America.
        https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Prunus_serotina
    </string>

    <string name="tree_24_name">Hawthorn</string>
    <string name="tree_24_des">Crataegus (/krəˈtiːɡəs/), commonly called hawthorn, quickthorn,
        thornapple, May-tree, whitethorn, or hawberry, is a genus of several hundred
        species of shrubs and trees in the family Rosaceae, native to temperate regions of the
        Northern Hemisphere.
        https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Crataegus
    </string>

    <string name="tree_25_name">Honey locust</string>
    <string name="tree_25_des">The honey locust (Gleditsia triacanthos), also known as the thorny
        locust or thorny honeylocust, is a deciduous tree in the family Fabaceae, native to central
        North America where it is mostly found in the moist soil of river valleys.
        https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Honey_locust
    </string>

    <string name="tree_26_name">Black locust</string>
    <string name="tree_26_des">Robinia pseudoacacia, commonly known in its native territory as
        black locust,[1] is a medium-sized hardwood deciduous tree, belonging to the tribe
        Robinieae. It is endemic to a few small areas of the United States, but it has been widely
        planted and naturalized elsewhere in temperate North America.
        https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Robinia_pseudoacacia
    </string>

    <string name="tree_27_name">Flowering dogwood</string>
    <string name="tree_27_des">Cornus florida, the flowering dogwood, is a species of flowering tree
        in the family Cornaceae native to eastern North America and northern Mexico.
        https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cornus_florida
    </string>

    <string name="tree_28_name">Silky dogwood</string>
    <string name="tree_28_des">Cornus amomum, the silky dogwood or kinnikinnik, is a species of
        dogwood native to the eastern United States.
        https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cornus_amomum
    </string>

    <string name="tree_29_name">Bladdernut</string>
    <string name="tree_29_des">Staphylea, called bladdernuts, is a small genus of 10 or 11 species
        of flowering plants in the family Staphyleaceae, native to temperate regions of the
        Northern Hemisphere.
        https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Staphylea
    </string>

    <string name="tree_30_name">Ohio buckeye</string>
    <string name="tree_30_des">The tree species Aesculus glabra is commonly known as Ohio buckeye,
        American buckeye, or fetid buckeye. A. glabra is one of 13–19 species of Aesculus. It is
        native primarily to the Midwestern and lower Great Plains regions of the United States.
        https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Aesculus_glabra
    </string>

    <string name="tree_31_name">Sugar maple</string>
    <string name="tree_31_des">Acer saccharum, the sugar maple or rock maple, is a species of
        flowering plant in the soapberry and lychee family Sapindaceae.
        https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Acer_saccharum
    </string>

    <string name="tree_32_name">Black maple</string>
    <string name="tree_32_des">Acer nigrum (black maple) is a species of maple closely related to
        A. saccharum (sugar maple), and treated by some authors as a subspecies of it, as
        Acer saccharum subsp. nigrum.
        https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Acer_nigrum
    </string>

    <string name="tree_33_name">Red maple</string>
    <string name="tree_33_des">Acer rubrum, the red maple, also known as swamp, water or soft maple,
        is one of the most common and widespread deciduous trees of eastern and central North
        America. The U.S. Forest service recognizes it as the most abundant native tree in eastern
        North America.
        https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Acer_rubrum
    </string>

    <string name="tree_34_name">Silver maple</string>
    <string name="tree_34_des">Acer saccharinum, commonly known as silver maple, creek maple,
        silverleaf maple, soft maple, large maple, water maple, swamp maple, or
        white maple, is a species of maple native to the eastern and central United States and
        southeastern Canada. It is one of the most common trees in the United States.
        https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Acer_saccharinum
    </string>

    <string name="tree_35_name">Box elder</string>
    <string name="tree_35_des">Acer negundo is a species of maple native to North America.
        Box elder, boxelder maple, ash-leaved maple, and maple ash are among its common names in
        the United States; in Canada it is commonly known as Manitoba maple and occasionally as
        elf maple.
        https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Acer_negundo
    </string>

    <string name="tree_36_name">White ash</string>
    <string name="tree_36_des">Fraxinus americana, the white ash or American ash, is a species of
        ash tree native to eastern and central North America.
        https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fraxinus_americana
    </string>

    <string name="tree_37_name">Green ash</string>
    <string name="tree_37_des">Fraxinus pennsylvanica, the green ash or red ash, is a species of
        ash native to eastern and central North America.
        https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fraxinus_pennsylvanica
    </string>

    <string name="tree_38_name">Pumpkin ash</string>
    <string name="tree_38_des">Fraxinus profunda, the pumpkin ash, is a species of Fraxinus (ash)
        native to eastern North America, primarily in the United States, with a scattered
        distribution on the Atlantic coastal plain and interior lowland river valleys.
        https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fraxinus_profunda
    </string>

    <string name="tree_39_name">Black ash</string>
    <string name="tree_39_des">Fraxinus nigra, the black ash, is a species of ash native to much of
        eastern Canada and the northeastern United States.
        https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fraxinus_nigra
    </string>

    <string name="tree_40_name">Buttonbush</string>
    <string name="tree_40_des">Cephalanthus occidentalis is a species of flowering plant in the
        coffee family, Rubiaceae, that is native to eastern and southern North America.
        https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cephalanthus_occidentalis
    </string>

    <string name="tree_41_name">Arrowwood</string>
    <string name="tree_41_des">Viburnum dentatum, southern arrowwood or arrowwood viburnum or
        roughish arrowwood, is a small shrub, native to the Eastern United States and Canada from
        Maine south to Northern Florida and Eastern Texas.
        https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Viburnum_dentatum
    </string>

    <string name="tree_42_name">Sweet viburnum</string>
    <string name="tree_42_des">Viburnum odoratissimum, commonly known as sweet viburnum, is a shrub
        or small tree in the family Adoxaceae. It is native to Asia, and commonly cultivated as a
        garden ornamental elsewhere.
        https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Viburnum_odoratissimum
    </string>


</resources>